<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: News | MidSouth Angora]]></title>
  <link href="http://midsouthangora.github.io/blog/categories/news/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://midsouthangora.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-04-13T20:52:24-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://midsouthangora.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dalton, Ga. Triple Show Results]]></title>
    <link href="http://midsouthangora.github.io/blog/2010/03/06/dalton-ga-triple-show-results/"/>
    <updated>2010-03-06T22:34:05-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://midsouthangora.github.io/blog/2010/03/06/dalton-ga-triple-show-results</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Here are the fast results of the Dalton, Ga. triple show. We will have the full results shortly.
<strong>Show 1</strong></p>

<p><strong>French Angoras</strong>
<strong>BOB</strong> &ndash; Colored Sr, Doe   &ndash;   Charlotte Schweikart
<strong>BOS</strong> &ndash; White Sr.  Buck  &ndash;   Charlotte Schweikart</p>

<p><strong>Satin Angoras</strong>
<strong>BOB</strong> &ndash; Colored  Sr. Doe  &ndash;   Sue Duncan
<strong>BOS</strong> &ndash; Colored  Sr. Buck &ndash; Sue Duncan</p>

<p><strong>English Angoras</strong>
<strong>BOB</strong> &ndash; White  Jr. Doe &ndash;  Lori White
<strong>BOS</strong> &ndash; Colored  Jr. Buck &ndash; Savanah Smith</p>

<p><strong>Giant Angoras</strong>
<strong>BOB</strong> &ndash; White 6/8  Doe Kim Gay</p>

<p><strong>Show 2</strong>
<strong>French Angoras</strong>
<strong>BOB</strong> &ndash;  White  Sr. Doe &ndash; Kim Gay
<strong>BOS</strong> &ndash; Colored Jr.  Buck  &ndash;   Charlotte Schweikart</p>

<p><strong>Satin Angoras</strong>
<strong>BOB</strong> &ndash; White  Sr. Doe  &ndash;   Gerald Buck
<strong>BOS</strong> &ndash; Colored  Sr. Buck &ndash; Sue Duncan</p>

<p><strong>English Angoras</strong>
<strong>BOB</strong> &ndash; Colored Sr. Doe &ndash;  Lori White
<strong>BOS</strong> &ndash; Colored  Jr. Buck &ndash; Savanah Smith</p>

<p><strong>Giant Angoras</strong>
<strong>BOB</strong> &ndash; White 6/8  Doe Kim Gay</p>

<p><strong>Show 3</strong>
<strong>French Angoras</strong>
<strong>BOB</strong> &ndash; Colored Sr, Doe   &ndash;   Charlotte Schweikart
<strong>BOS</strong> &ndash; Colored Sr.  Buck  &ndash;   Charlotte Schweikart
<strong>
Satin Angoras</strong>
<strong>BOB</strong> &ndash; White  Sr. Doe  &ndash;   Kim Gay
<strong>BOS</strong> &ndash; Colored  Sr. Buck &ndash; Sue Duncan</p>

<p><strong>English Angoras</strong>
<strong>BOB</strong> &ndash; Colored Sr. Doe &ndash;  Maxine Asher &ndash; Perkins
<strong>BOS</strong> &ndash; Colored  Jr. Buck &ndash; Lori White</p>

<p><strong>Giant Angoras</strong>
<strong>BOB</strong> &ndash; White 6/8  Doe Kim Gay</p>

<p>If you missed the show, you missed out on a great time!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fast Approching Nationals]]></title>
    <link href="http://midsouthangora.github.io/blog/2010/02/22/fast-approching-nationals/"/>
    <updated>2010-02-22T15:52:01-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://midsouthangora.github.io/blog/2010/02/22/fast-approching-nationals</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Well we are getting close to the Dalton, Ga. shows now. I have checked with those in charge of the trophies for the NARBC Nationals and our Mid-South Angora Specialty show and all the trophies are ready! Yippee! Keep your fingers crossed that things go well for us. Everyone has worked hard hopefully it will be a smooth ride.</p>

<p>I have talked to several people from far off who are planning on coming to the show. This is a great chance to get new stock that would otherwise be out of our reach to get other than shipping! The Nationals will probably not be around here again for some time so do take advantage of this one close by us!</p>

<p>If you have items for the raffle table please bring them with you. It looks like we will have a fantastic raffle this year thanks to all our hard working members. There will be a wide range of very nice things so please plan to participate in that.</p>

<p>All in all I think we will have a great time. If my dvd recorder works this year I plan on getting videos of the shows. They will be available just as soon as I get back and get them uploaded to the web site. If you would like to purchase a video let me know. Terri Greathouse will be our photographer again this year. We should have some great pictures for viewing also.</p>

<p>More later&hellip;&hellip;</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our Entry Form Is Up!]]></title>
    <link href="http://midsouthangora.github.io/blog/2010/01/22/our-entry-form-is-up/"/>
    <updated>2010-01-22T20:46:47-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://midsouthangora.github.io/blog/2010/01/22/our-entry-form-is-up</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1>Enter our shows online</h1>

<p>This link will take you to the <a href="http://angora.saga-designs.com">show entry form</a>.</p>

<p>You will be redirected to the entry form. You can enter all your info like name, address, telephone number, email, ect. AND the number of rabbits you are entering.   After you enter all the basic info click submit. You will proceed to the form for entering your rabbit data. After you enter all your rabbit info click submit. You will be redirected back to Mid-South web site. A copy will be emailed to the address you entered and to the show secretary. You will receive an &ldquo;I got your entries&rdquo; back from the show secretary.</p>

<p>If you have any problems or questions just email me.</p>

<p>Thanks and hope to meet you at the show!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Membership Contest]]></title>
    <link href="http://midsouthangora.github.io/blog/2009/12/22/membership-contest/"/>
    <updated>2009-12-22T11:54:29-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://midsouthangora.github.io/blog/2009/12/22/membership-contest</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We are having a <strong>membership contest.</strong> We will have a first, second, and third prizes to be awarded. The contest will run from now &ndash; Dec. 22 to Feb. 30th. Prizes will be awarded at the Dalton show in March or mailed. There are only a few rules so have fun! I will try to keep a running count if I can keep up with Jacque! LOL</p>

<h3>First Prize &ndash; A beautiful angora bunny donated by Amanda Politino. (bunny of her choosing) The prize bunny will be delivered to the Dalton show in March. If you will not be attending or can not get someone to pick it up for you an alternative prize of Mixed Fiber will be awarded.</h3>

<h3>Second Prize &ndash; 8 oz. of Angora fiber</h3>

<h3>Third Prize &ndash; A very nice slicker brush</h3>

<p>We will not have to many rules here. If you are not a current member you still may participate in the contest. All you will be required to do is join first, then start getting members. Please be sure that when you send someone to join that you remind them to mention your name or we can&rsquo;t give you credit. :) There is a place in the cart for a referral name.</p>

<p><em>Rules &ndash; To receive a prize, the minimum of 3 people will have to be referred and join.</em></p>

<p>Have fun and hope to see everyone at Dalton this year!<img src="http://www.midsouthangora.com/angora/wp-content/uploads/2009/12/basket1-100x100.jpg" alt="basket" /></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big New Look]]></title>
    <link href="http://midsouthangora.github.io/blog/2009/12/18/big-new-look/"/>
    <updated>2009-12-18T19:14:08-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://midsouthangora.github.io/blog/2009/12/18/big-new-look</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We rolled out our new web site today. We plan to add a lot of new features shortly to make it a fun stay here at Mid-South.</p>

<p>It is also time to renew Mid-South membership. You can conveniently renew or join here on the web site. Just click on the icon in the right column of the site and it will take you right to PayPal. Just fill out the short form and you can pay with PayPal or a credit card. A very quick and simple form, along with totally secure transaction. Come join us!</p>

<p>The latest on the NARBC Nationals will be posted in a day or two so keep a look out for that. We hope you are planning to attend the Nationals in March 2010!</p>

<p>We will have an on line show entry form available for the Nationals and the Angora specialty show for your entry convenience. There will be a Mid-South raffle table so please donate any extra things you have laying around. You can send them to Sarah Schumate or Kim Gay. You may also bring them with you to the show with you.</p>

<p>[caption id=&ldquo;attachment_147&rdquo; align=&ldquo;aligncenter&rdquo; width=&ldquo;150&rdquo; caption=&ldquo;Gone With The Wool 2010&rdquo;]<img src="http://www.midsouthangora.com/angora/wp-content/uploads/2009/12/marchlogo3.gif" alt="Gone With The Wool 2010" />[/caption]</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
